The Move Inventory workflow allows you to manage and distribute your Amazon
warehousing and distribution or AWD inventory.
You have the option to choose
SKUs to be auto replenished to FBA when your FBA inventory gets low.
When auto
replenishment isn't enough to meet expected sales, you can request additional
inventory be sent to FBA.
You can also send your AWD inventory in bulk to your
own warehouse, third-party warehouses, wholesalers, and distributors with AWD's
multi-channel distribution capability.
To initiate a move, select Move Inventory
on the AWD program page.
If you are moving within the Amazon network, select
FBA replenishment under Distribution Type.
If you are moving to off Amazon
locations on the Move From Storage page, select Off Amazon Distribution under
Distribution Type.
Then select the origin warehouse from the move from drop-down
and the destination from the destination drop-down.
To add channels and
destinations, click Manage Destinations when selecting the Off Amazon
Distribution option in the Move Inventory workflow.
Then enter the channel and
destination information, then click Save.
Next, select the SKUs you want to move
by entering the number of boxes to move.
Click Confirm to confirm the move and
then click Review Move Request.
On the Review Move Request page, confirm the
move request by clicking Confirm Move Request.
Once you see the confirmation
page, your move request has been completed.